<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">COVID-19</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">COVID‑19 pandemic</string>
    <string name="add_comment">Add Comment</string>
    <string name="article_text">The COVID-19 pandemic, also known as the coronavirus pandemic, is an ongoing pandemic of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) caused by severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2).[1] The disease was first identified in December 2019 in Wuhan, China.[4] The outbreak was declared a Public Health Emergency of International Concern in January 2020, and a pandemic in March 2020. As of 14 October 2020, more than 38 million cases have been confirmed, with more than 1.08 million deaths attributed to COVID-19.[6]
        \n\n for more information https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/COVID-19_pandemic.
        \n\n The disease spreads most often when people are physically close.[b] It spreads very easily and sustainably through the air, primarily via small droplets and sometimes in aerosols, as an infected person breathes, coughs, sneezes, talks, or sings.[8][9] It may also be transmitted via contaminated surfaces, although this has not been conclusively demonstrated.[9][10][11] It can spread from an infected person for up to two days prior to symptom onset and from people who are asymptomatic.[9] People remain infectious for seven to twelve days in moderate cases and up to two weeks in severe cases.[9][12]
        \n\n Common symptoms include fever, cough, fatigue, breathing difficulties, and loss of smell. Complications may include pneumonia and acute respiratory distress syndrome. The incubation period is typically around five days but may range from one to 14 days.[12] There are several vaccine candidates in development, although none have proven their safety and efficacy. There is no known specific antiviral medication, so primary treatment is currently symptomatic.[13]
        \n\n Recommended preventive measures include hand washing, covering mouth or wearing face mask when sneezing or coughing, social distancing, disinfecting surfaces, ventilation and air-filtering, and monitoring and self-isolation if exposed or symptomatic. Travel restrictions, lockdowns, workplace hazard controls, and facility closures have been implemented. Many places have also worked to increase testing capacity and trace contacts of the infected. These have caused social and economic disruption, including the largest global recession since the Great Depression.[14] Extreme poverty and global famines are affecting hundreds of millions, inflamed by supply shortages. Many events, the environment and education systems have also been affected. Misinformation about the virus has circulated globally. There have been many incidents of xenophobia and racism against Chinese people and against those perceived as being Chinese or as being from areas with high infection rates.[15]
    </string>
</resources>